Four empty spaces in the room
A silent echo in the gloom
We crossed the way to find a shore But left behind
what came before
The city lights are cold and bright A different
sky A different night
Standing in the hollow square
Reaching out but no one's there We forged the
ember, paint the sky To keep the fading embers
high In the hollow square
The cables hung, the circuits clocked
To mask the quiet down below
We sequence notes to fill the void A symphony
we re-employ
Just to remain, to hold the line And reconstruct
The grand design
Standing in the hollow square
Reaching out but no one's there Reforge the
armor, paint the sky To keep the fading embers
high In the hollow square
The stage is smaller, but the sound is deep A
promise that we swore to keep
Through the silence, hear the spark We light the
beacons in the dark
Standing in the hollow square
Reaching out but no one's there We forge the
armor, paint the sky To keep the fading embers
high In hollow square
We hold
the line